Greenbaum, Marcia Arbitration Files 6208
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Arbitration A - C, 2002. (Box 15)
  - Branford, CT and AAA Branford Education Association Insurance Premiums (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Branford Board of Education and Branford Board of Education Association Joint Exhibit 1 (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Board of Ed. And Branford Board of Ed. Assn. Exhibits (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Branford Board of Education/BEA (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Burrillville Racing Association and AAA Local 334 J. Pardi Reimbursement (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Central Maine Power Company and AAA Local 1837 R. Lee Discharge (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Coca Cola Bottling Co. and AAA Local 1035 Wages Classification (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 Local 1663 Julia Reyes (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 Daneen Henry (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFCSME Council 4 Mitchell (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFCSME Council 4 Institutional (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 #08-5035 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFCSME Council 4 n. Rodriguez et al. (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - State of Connecticut and OL AFSCME Council 4 #08-5116 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 DeWayne Rodwell (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Connecticut Institute for the Blind and AAA NeHCEU 1199 Susp. And Final Warning (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Cranston Print Works and AAA GRTR Northeastern JT. Bd. E. Stark Suspension (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Arbitration D - J, 2002. (Box 16)
  - Fort Meyers Beach Fire Control and Unjust Discipline Southwest FL Prof. FF & Paramed (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Frito-Lay and John Jackson (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - GAF Materials Corp. and IB Teamsters Local 25 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Georgia-Pacific Corp. and AAA Local 1-0080 Bickford Disc. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Hartford, CT Bd. Of Education and AAA Hartford Federation of Teachers (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Hartford, CT Board of Education and AAA Hartford Federation of Teachers Vinagre (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Hartford Board of Education and AAA Hartford Federation Teachers LaPenna (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Hartford Board of Education and AAA Hartford Federation of Teachers (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Hovensa and FMCS Local 8526 Bertwin Martin (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Local 1991 Dr. Djahed (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Jackson Memorial Hospital and FMCS Local 1991 Perfect Rating Joyce Lucas (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Local 1991 Lynn Squiuawe (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - AAA Lynn Suillacote and Public Health Trust Arbitration pg. 1-48 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Local 1991 (Lynn Squillacote) and Public Health Trust/Jackson Memorial Hospital Arbitration pg. 49-176 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Local 1991 and Public Health Trust/Jackson Memorial Hospital pg. 177-343 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Local 1991 and Public Health Trust/Jackson Memorial Hospital pg. 365-461 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Local 1991 and Public Health Trust/Jackson Memorial Hospital pg. 474-689 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Local 1991 and Public Health Trust/Jackson Memorial Hospital pg. 716-854 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Local 1991 and Public Health Trust/Jackson Memorial Hospital pg. 855-1052 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Local 1991 and Public Health Trust/Jackson Memorial Hospital pg. 1053-1127 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Local 1991 and Public Health Trust/Jackson Memorial Hospital pg. 1118-1298 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Local 1991 and Public Health Trust/Jackson Memorial Hospital pg. 1118-1298 (condensed) (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Arbitration M - W, 2002. (Box 17)
  - Marta (Atlanta, GA) and FMCS ATU Division 732 Job Bids (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 732 Arbitration Hearing pg. 1-188 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Electric Co. and Local 329 Procedure for Requesting Aid (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Electric Co. and Local 446 Violation of E-Men Agreement (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Mass. Institute of Technology and AAA MIT Campus Police Association (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Memorial Hospital of Rhode Island and AAA Local 5082 2 ER Credit (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Memorial Hospital of RI and AAA Local 5082 ER Schedule (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - City of Miramar and FMCS Local 101 Williams Termination (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Muscle Shoals Minerals and FMCS Local 200-03 Job Bid Disqualification (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - New Hampshire Ball Bearing and AAA Change in Wash-up Procedure (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Plymouth county Sheriff's Dept. and AAA Association of County Employees Smoking Policy (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Saint Camillus Health Center and AAA NEHCEU Local 1199 Burke Termination (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Sara Lee Bakery and FMCS Local 611 Fort Payne, AL Holiday Pay (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. and AAA Local 791 Esvin Damian Termination (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Shaw's Supermarkets and AAA Local 791 Brenna Cibley Termination (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Sky Chefs National Agreement and hotel EES & Restaurant EES Union (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Stafford Board of Education and AAA Stafford Education Association Insurance Premium Holday (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Tandet Center for Continuing Care and AAA Local 1199 Goodrich Suspension (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Union Leader Corporation and AAA Manchester Newspaper Guild (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Verizon and Local 2222 Victor Pagluica (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Verizon and MREP Local 2323 Termination of M. Villella (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Warwick, RI Police Dept. and AAA Warwick for Lodge #7 Sick and Job Injury Money (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Co. Exhibit #4 - Video Tape (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Arbitration: Winchester Schools - Dr. DePaulo Discharge, 2002. (Box 18)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Arbitration Vol. 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 3 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 4 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 5 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 6 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol, 7 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 8 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 8 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 9 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 10 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 11 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 12 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 13 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 14 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 15 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 16 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 17 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 18 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Vol. 19 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Association Exhibit 19 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Arbitration - Winchester SC/T, 2002. (Box 19)
  - Winchester Education Association Exhibit 40 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Winchester Education Association Exhibits 39, 41-46 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Winchester Education Association Exhibits 15-38 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Exhibits (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Winchester Education Association Exhibits 1-13 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools Exhibits 1-52 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Joint Exhibits 1-4 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Draft (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Chronology Pages with Additions (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Notes (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Information (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Brief on Behalf of Petitioner (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Related Cases (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Notes (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Brief of Winchester School Committee (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Notes (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association Award (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Winchester, MA Public Schools and Winchester Education Association (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Arbitration Awards A - D, 2003. (Box 20)
  - Ansonia Cooper & Brass and United Steelworkers Job Combination (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Aramark Educational Services and Local 217 Wesleyan University (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Chariho Reg. and Chariho Esp. K. McNulty termination (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - City of Chicopee and Local 1459 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Coca-Cola Bottling Co. and Local 677 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 T. Johnson (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 T. Johnson (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 Opinion and Award (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 Lisa Bracey (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 Linda Carson (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - State Exhibits 1-34 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - State Exhibit 35 - Unemployment Compensation (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - State Exhibits 36-51 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Union Exhibits 1-63 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - State of Connecticut and Local 2663 Opinion and Award (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 Institutional (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Cumberland Farms and Jennifer Gardner (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Cumberland School Com. And Cumberland Teachers Term Life Insurance Benefit (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Delta Pride Catfish and Local 1529 D. Pembleton Unjust Termination (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Disability Rights and Local 2320 L. Dowell suspension (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Arbitration Awards E - S, 2003. (Box 21)
  - Eastern Maine Medical Center and AAA Maine State Nurses Association - Michelle LeBlanc (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Exelon Corp. Comed.and Local 15 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Freetown/Lakeville and AAA Ed Association of Freetown - P. Mueller Workload (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Frito-Lay Inc. Employee Arbitration and Gregory Shelton (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Frito-Lay Inc. and Local Union 633- Carton Pay (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Frito-Lay Inc. and Teamsters Local 633 - Raymond Cutter Suspension (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Frito-Lay, Inc. Employment Arb. And Jim Perry 2003 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - GAF Materials Corp. and Teamsters Local 25 - St. Pierre (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Green Mountain Power Co. (2003) and IBEW Local 300 - Steven Moore Discharge (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Hartford Public Schools and AAA Hartford Federation of Professionals - Matos Longevity (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Hartford Board of Ed. And AAA Hartford Federation of Teachers - Masters Pay (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Hialeah Shores and SEIU Local 1199 - Health and Life Insurance (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Hilltop Health Center and AAA NEHCEU - Delores Hamilton (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Hollingsworth & Vose Co. and Pace Local I-880 - David Harkins Discharge (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Lawrence School Com. And AAA Lawrence teacher Union - Joan Metz (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - MBTA and AAA MBTA Police Association - Task Force (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Mansfield, MA School Comm. And AAA Mansfield Building and Grounds - Suspension Connolly (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Monadnock Paper Mills and AAA Local I-472 - Rick Chicoine (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Town of North Providence, RI and AAA Local 1033 - Suspension David Esposito (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Parkview Specialty Hospital and AAA - Holiday Week Specials (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Plaza Nursing Center and FMCS SEIU Local 1199 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Quinnipiac University and AAA Quinnipiac Faculty Federation - Professor Arrey (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Randolph Public Schools and AAA Randolph Education Association - Layoffs RR Staff (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Reed & Barton Silversmiths and AAA - DeMello Return to Prior Position (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - State of Rhode Island and AAA Local 580 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - State of Rhode Island and AAA Council 94 - Sheila Rourke Suspension (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Rhode Island Convention Center and FMCS Local 217 - Banquet Server (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Rogers Corp. and AAA Local I-46 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. and AAA UFCW Local 791 - Personal Days (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. and AAA UFCW Local 791 - Personal Days (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Shaw's Supermarkets and AAA UFCW Local 791 - Deli Manager (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. and AAA Local 791 - Mathieu Suspension (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. and AAA Local 791 - Meyer Memorial Day wk (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. and AAA Local 791 - Hayrol Silverio (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Shepard Exposition Services and FMCS Local 835 - Job Steward Payment (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Arbitration Awards S - Z, 2003. (Box 22)
  - City of Somerville, MA and AAA Somerville Municipal EES Association (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - UNICCO Service Company and AAA SEIU Local 254 - J. Nova Termination (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - United States Mint. And Local 1023 - Unsafe Conditions (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - US Department of Transportation Federal Aviation Administration and NAATS (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - US Department of Transportation Federal Aviation Administration and NAATS (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - MREP Case 179 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Windham Hospital and AAA Windham United Employees Local 5099 - E. Musial (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - WHDH-TV and AAA IBEW Local 1228 - S. Smith Suspension (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Windham Hospital and AA Windham United EES - Porter Evaluation (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - City of Warwick v. Edward Pelletier Record (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - City of Warwick v. Edward Pelleier Record (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - City of Warwick, RI and AAA Lodge 7 - Pelletier Suspension (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Town of Smithfield Fire Dept. and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 2050, 2003. (Box 23)
  - Town of Smithfield and AAA IAFF Local 2050 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Smithfield and Local 2050 Joint Exhibits and Collective Bargaining Agreement (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Smithfield and Local 2050 Union Exhibits 1-25 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Smithfield and Local 2050 Union Exhibits Cont. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Smithfield and Local 2050 Union Exhibits 38-71 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Smithfield and Local 2050 Union Exhibits 27-36 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Smithfield and Local 2050 Union Exhibits 72-78; Town Exhibit 7 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Smithfield and Local 2050 Town Exhibits Part 1 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Smithfield and Local 2050 Town Exhibits Part 2 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Smithfield and Local 2050 Town Exhibits Part 3 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Smithfield and Local 2050 Town Exhibits Part 4 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Smithfield and Local 2050 Town Exhibits Part 5 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Smithfield and Local 2050 Town Exhibits Part 5 (Box 23, Folder 12)